gets to behave, where prayers don't kneel, they shimmer and cave, in the smoke of a bell and the salt of a sigh, a circle of women stood under, no sky, not one but a chorist and shadows in bloom.
Miss me
The holy mistake that corrects you at night
They are the mirror that won't flatter pain
They are the river that eats every chain
Not angels, not demons, no!
So I listen instead and I learned how to trust ten wins in a temple ten notes in my
thank you for watching that hey um well you know what yeah they're losers but i needed them to do
that for my own reasons basically because i'm too forgiving and i will like keep having them on forever
i mean it's like i just needed to like i just needed them to do that the episode's gone it's deleted
They'll they're gone. They'll never happen. Oh, I just got a but a couple couple small penis Mexican guys. I
Mean
You know, they called they called Mexican Mexican they called their dick pinga
It's not they don't I don't even think they have a
They're just ingas. I don't know. They're just
gauze. Oh
It was nothing
Sigs penis has been exposed. I mean, it's like now we all know
How small it is. Oh, you're lucky me. You know, I don't want you. I don't want your eyes to see that kind of thing
Yeah, I mean it's like and
Then and then 300 glow that was just gay porn on his screen. So we know what's on his phone
That that was what he got too quick is
so
They can go suck each other's dicks for the rest of their lives.
I just needed them to just reveal themselves,
which is what my show is a lot about is like people just revealing themselves.
That's why I'll have people on over and over again until they do.
Anyway, so Alexandra Mayers, she's doing some Bible study.
If I'm going to go to a church,
Mean it's called the Church of Jezebel or something like that. I mean what what the fuck are we?
Okay, I'll tell okay fine. I
Get a former porn star becomes a Christian. She's right here. Here's Lunar. I get that. That's fine
But you're gonna remain as
Non-forgiving as hateful, I mean it's like
That I mean, it's like do you understand Christ?
You've been watching her videos on me. Yeah
Do you understand Christ Alexandra? You know a Christ message, you know, it's called Christianity has to do with Jesus Christ
It's not about worshiping Jezebel of Kings. Oh, there he is Jesus in the chat. What's up Jesus? Oh
Look perfect
You to remove the one you uploaded. Oh, oh, yeah, okay. I'll watch it
Yeah, I got it in time. I don't know. I don't I'd never really wanted to lecture her on Christianity. I
Never did
Whatever it is
She ain't it
Hateful slanders she's like the people that basically put Jesus on the cross so
Yeah
Oh, yeah, the roll of paper. Yeah, Lenore
That's a point and then she says oh
Yeah
Let's see you want to
But um, yeah, that was that was the guys that you have to admit that was pretty cool
Say Jesus name and that's the real Jesus I think
But um, you know, it's about even I don't care if you if you
Did I know I'm not saying she did but I'm saying if there's a porn star that
Does gang bangs or whatever I don't care
I believe they can be Christian Christian Christian is a lot about forgiveness and redemption
And it's like there's people that are murderers that find Christ and it's like but it's about kind of like, you know
changing your ways a little bit.
I saw a glimmer of hope in her when I met her
because I've heard all the stories and stuff,
but just like Bita had thought,
like, you know, she had changed.
I thought that something had changed.
Look how judgmental she is.
Now she's like throwing like the, yeah.
So, I know Alex is mad at me,
I mean, now I got both Alex,
that both the Alex is mad at me, right?
Can't I can't help what other people would other people think of Alexing some if Alexander thinks I'm a moron if she thinks I'm a spiritual trafficker
Not too much of my business
It's like the the question is what is Christ like
Think Jesus would have gone around screaming about traffickers and
You know, don't, you know, don't forgive people.
I mean, it's like, I don't think so.
Just think about it.
And I'm not saying, oh, I'm this great Christian or whatever.
I mean, I've studied all religions
and it's like, I think all religions are,
have some validity somewhere.
I mean, it's like, I worship the goddess of leftovers
and outcasts and music and voice and art
and stuff like that, right?
Um, but I do love Jesus' message, but if you're going to go around saying I'm this Christian
and I am holier than thou and like this and that, Jesus was not judgmental like that.
I'm sorry.
I mean, she won't listen to this or whatever I know.
Yeah.
Me I'm a spiritual trafficking moron. Okay, Alex, but you but you missed my you missed my whole beginning of the speech
But you're now you there you go. Okay, go ahead. Go ahead Alex. I hate me
She feels I'm suicide baby and blame her
I never said all I said was that
She was like you understand that they're there the
One's baiting right you understand that they're the ones baiting
She said she wanted to be charged for slander
Yeah
What does she say she said people fuck dogs?
You know, I mean all this kind of stuff, right?
Who who isn't a trafficker in this community according to her, okay?
McQueen you go over to her. What's what's wrong with McQueen McQueen am I okay like
Alex you don't even have a
like
You understand it's my it's mine
But you you're when you're so Alex is wanting to like disconnect. I mean this Alex to okay
But you have to just put guys and you're being watched about you know, I'll keep you as I'll keep you
I plan the two inch invasion
You know why?
Because I'm too forgiving and I'll keep letting them on until I until they fucking did something like that
I needed I needed I needed to give him a chance to prove it. How much did I pace it? Why would I pace pace it?
What are you talking about?
Alex I mean, I mean is there something about the names that letters a and l
That makes people insane. I mean, come on Alexander. It's me
Alex I
Want to shake her too sometimes not not in a kind of mean way. I just want to say hello
It's me you don't recognize me I
Really would think Alexander McQueen would you think I'm paying sick
You should pay me
She paid me for all the all the rumble publicity he got
You want to undock, okay?
It was great to know you I mean it's like if you didn't get it you don't get it
That tells something about me, too. That tells the thing about you, too
How about this?
People using the threat of self-harm or SUICID an effort to manipulate or control others
online
suggests
to be and
No, you're not undocking you're staying around
Any I need you here
Okay
Or control others
suggests to be an element
That's on the rise. Well, I mean come on. Can we be like more like silly about it? It's on the rise
How stupid does that sound it sounds straight out of chat GPT
Come on, maybe original about it. Maybe original Alexandra. Come on
I have to be a little bit original with my way I write stuff.
I know I generate images and, you know, the sounds of the music,
but all is on there.
Come on.
It's on the rise.
What does that mean?
I mean, and then it gets, it's better.
It gets rich.
Join me for my Bible study join me for my Bible study really oh
No, no, you're Alex here. You're stuck with me. I mean not not Alexander mayor Alexander McQueen my my I need you for security
You're like my best friend stop it stop it can't lose another best friend stop it you need to
To realize I know I know what I'm doing. I'm not as dumb as I look. I know I look dumb, right?
But don't you know me better than that? I just needed him to do it. So I never have to deal with him again
My shows don't hurt
I'm gonna be mad at someone be mad damn beta and and alexandra. They struck my channel
They're the ones continuing to slander and all this stuff. It's sick and
300 glory just retards
They're basically, I mean, I have a brain cell away from,
you know, meaning to be wiped.
Yes, sir.
Psyche!
Yo, can I ask you something?
Yeah.
Are we best friends?
Yeah, go ahead.
We're acquaintances. Whoa, what it's very strong very strong. Very small. I don't know. I was just kidding. I'm just playing
I won't hurt. I ain't gonna lie. Oh, okay. Come on. Give me a hug. I was just kidding. I was just kidding. Damn
No, no, no, we're no, we're not best friends
My best friends if you're my best friend, right? Oh, come on
I was just kidding this guy that might don't get my sense of humor my best friends hurt me
So I just I just need
Yeah, no questions asked. My best my I just want friends. I just want I just want a true friend not
I don't need a best friend because then they always just end up like fucking me over, right?
even acquaintance
I mean, it's like our
Less likely to fuck me over than my best friends. Look at look at my record
Yeah, be the
Alexandra Emma, it's like oh
They're just succubuses
Second, so what happened to the last stream who got you long got me
I don't know if he was host if you put it was a pretty up a picture of a dolphin giving birth or
Gays, I don't know what it was. It just didn't look right, right? But it was I can tell what it was. Okay
We could have been someone milking a cow. I don't know. I mean, it's just it always saw was
Just him holding up a phone. Really. I don't know what the fuck it was. I don't think anybody
AI or anything will pick that up. I mean, but I believe
Really, I'm like who porn bomb you dude. What I don't know. I don't know
I think it was him in him and say, you know fucking and stuff on the video. I would do their home
There's our home video
And I don't care if I get killed by the Mexican mafia over this. I mean, it's like, you know
They should know better
Okay
Yeah, anyway, I mean, it's like really I mean it's like wow
My my spiritual trafficking days are numbered I
Only have I only have I only have so long to spiritually traffic everybody
I don't know where trying to get people to to heaven or something like that, but I mean
What do they think I'm trying to traffic people?
Don't talk about traffic to me. If I can't ride a bike, I think I'm safe, too. I think I'm safe, too.
I've been pormombed over a hundred times with a lot bigger cocks than SIGs.
I mean, it's like, really. I don't even know if it qualifies as a cock.
I think it qualifies as a large vagina.
Yeah, that was just there. I mean, I mean, it's like what else would he have? I mean, I don't know. It's like
You know that they're fucking. I mean, it's like they
That you think they're joking about it whenever people joke
Sometimes that's where you find the truth
I don't know who could fit. I don't think their dicks would have been each other's butts. I think they have to use their their like
fingers and stuff, but
Yeah, Lenore get the roll
We're doing it didn't learn at the house
Someone want to roll
Tricks you hit the roll
Here's a trick doesn't really want it
Yeah, I think Lenore's out the door. Lenore, Lenore's out the door. She, she went outside to play.
You in it? Here, take that. You know it's Trix's birthday yesterday. Oh, two years ago? Uh-oh. Here.
It was funny when there, she got the roll yesterday. She got, she was just roll, she, oh, look at it. You got it. You got it. Trix got it.
Oh, Trix.
What the roll?
I mean, this is the
If this is like the size of
Well, I'm just trying to think like I need I need like a smaller. Oh, here we go. I want Arthur's thing
You need like
I don't know. I think here this is the size of sig
I'm making it look too big.
It's like a little, it's just a head.
It's basically just a head, and you open it,
and you see 300 closed mouth.
I mean, they're just so lame.
Can you imagine?
Oh, let's go harass this guy.
I mean, it's like, get a life.
Yes, sir.
Eleanor, did you tell Eleanor what happened?
My cat. Yeah
Yeah, I've uh, I told her that
Um, I saw some Mexican jumping beans
Is she like wow? I have a bigger penis
Yeah, Lenore's like I have a bigger cock than those guys
That's what she said and then Eleanor is crazy man. She's a crazy cat
That's actually that's what Lenora short for. It's a short for Eleanor. Yeah, I know. Yeah
You saw the picture right you saw that yes, you scribe that picture
Oh my goodness like when I tell you and I'm not being sarcastic when I tell you his bush his pubes
Are so much longer than his actual penis. It's insane. Yeah, man. How's that? I mean, it's even like, you know
the hairs on his head like really I mean it's like yeah that I mean he has long hair so that
doesn't really count but like a bush like a bush you know like the uh an 80s bush a 70s bush I need
to be careful because he'll he Alex will get mad at me if I don't check him out carefully hold on
one second so make sure uh hop on McQueen where's McQueen at hop on brother he's coming hold on one
Come on McQueen
Volume is low. Can we bring it up? Yeah, I'll put it up. What did that happen? How long did that go that it happened?
Did what happen?
When I say show this little peepee how long ago did it happen because I'm just coming out of the ring
I can't really hear him. Okay. I got it. I got his volume home sick show this peepee about
Oh, that's because he had my volume on zero of Arthur. That's why you couldn't hear me because you but now it's on 200
So my god, oh my god, Lola just brought in a mouse Lola
Brought in a mouse. How long did it take for that? Oh my god the rage to end
Oh my god, it was yeah, I was you were you were who?
What does that say about me though my anti-gay my anti-social do I just go into a rage when I see a cock like well
I don't know
porn bomb your anti-porn bomb
You're anti-porn. No, I'm not really I am anti-porn mama. That was a different type of porn mama
Especially when somebody I've sat on panel with for a long time on other channels. That was weird
Yeah, you don't think that fucked with me, bro
But you know what? I want that to be like a lesson to everybody just like nobody let them on anymore
Like just listen no no no no let him on cuz you all gonna let him on dick. So I gotta face the fact
Because you like that shit, whatever. I'm gonna tell you not to not let on but I don't know I'm laughing at it man
But who's who is crazy, right?
What crazy
Commented
I was like, you're so mad that I had your mic at zero for like 20 minutes. You even notice. Yeah. I know I noticed it after I watched
I'm like, yo, bro, this ha ha didn't hear a word and good because I was going crazy
You were screaming to the top of your lungs. Oh, that was fucked up
Fuck me man. Yes, you saw his little pee pee
Yeah, bro, it's disgusting
You guys are used to that your little freak ops in the back like you guys do that. I'm not used to that
You'll do that. You'll show your dick to each other and jerk off in the back. Freak off. I don't like you used to that
You guys are used to that. I'm not used to that. No, right? That should piss me the fuck off, bro
That's your glow. I jerked off from in the backstage. That was disgusting. That was the most disgusting thing
I swear to God if he was in front of me, I would have killed him see I would and I
The fatal rage that I went on the panel, I would have went in real life.
And so if he did it in front of me, I would have killed him.
I wouldn't be able to control my rage.
And then cops would have came and I'd be in jail forever.
And then I would be like, why did I kill him?
Workers are, bro.
Like now I'm laughing about it a little bit.
Like now I'm kind of laughing like, haha.
Like I'm trying to step out of that rage.
But yo, that was not funny, man.
I can't people man. She is this fuck that shit will get you killed here, bro
I don't know where you Californians or you fucking freaks come from
Who's that shit in New York? You're dead. You're dead
Yeah, you're gonna he's not from New York
Yeah, maybe I'll stay in New York enough with your city. No, no, I'm saying the state upstate there you go
Freakland he's upstate and freak will
He's a lot fucking weirdo, bro. Oh my god, the cat is crunching on a mouse under my table
Gusting and the fucker fucked up or is the psyche's gonna let him off and then he left 300
Yo, it's almost like you know, this is what I think psyche you're asking for it
You know, they're gonna pump on you like it in a way
Three hundred go comes up two minutes later and phone bombs you like how stupid
You have to be so you know if I ever see 300 glow and sick up here
I'm just gonna say like he's the biggest idiot that ever lived in my life, right?
Right
Literally, you know, you're Jesus Christ. You're Jesus Christ the loser that forgives
Oh, you're the biggest moron on the face of the planet
Okay, they're never gonna come on out. I promise. I swear to God, bro
Don't is this not my channel
I'm just saying how I'm gonna view you if I do see them up here because I already viewed you that way a little
Like this guy lets him on after on after pomo after pomo after pomo
Obviously, it's a trend. He likes it. He allows it. He loves it and he's gonna allow them again
Again
And that's a fact
and that's weird it's getting weird now but i don't even think you're gay that's one thing
but uh you know making on gay people go through this shit seeing cox like that's weird bro what if
what what if a woman porn bomb with her vagina that'd be great but they don't do like
So we're gonna be in this mess of that happened. Unfortunately. We got fat fucks in their kitchen
We're gonna little pee pee and you laugh you get
Dead the panel and let them up again tomorrow and they put the little pee pee again
And you laugh and you let them up again the next day and they put their dick out and you laugh
8b or c it's one of the other my man one plus one makes two
see if you want to see the smallest wiener you've ever seen but you make fun of it by trying to deflect
you keep letting these people on that porn bomb you for a two years straight and after tonight
if you still let them
I didn't see you know I didn't see me but you like it though. It's your channel
So who am I to tell you not to let little pee pee boy up because you love it you fucking love it just admit it to me
That's all I want to hear is say Alex. I love it. I actually do love it
I'll let them on forever and they can pull mom and I'll just end the channel and laugh and I'm a fucking freak
Just say it but don't act like you're so many things take like oh
Everyday oh my god
You allow you piece of shit. You know, they're gonna do it. They've been doing it for 10 years
And when they do you laugh please wave at the camera like that's not cool, bro
I don't come from the same mentality as you in that sense
Okay, he's waving. Okay. I mean, let's let him glaze up. Okay. He's on the camera ladies
Hey, what's going on? Hi, how are you? I don't think I've met you
You've met me. Get up and show us your cock and make this man happy. Just stand up for your cock out
So psyche can be happy, bro. Cuz that's what he wants to see
He's not going to hi, how are you tonight I
Know of you you probably know of me. I've just
This is a night
One of those nights. I'm gonna stop in here for a little bit
Okay, cool. Well, nice to meet you. Hey, I'm not gonna do any shit to you. Okay. Thank you. I mean, it's like I just don't
I'll just have to I would just okay. We know he he he welcomes it. He welcomes it
If you turn over and put your pants and show your asshole, you're good here my man
But you know, don't be boring sitting in a chair smoking a cigarette do something shortcut
Do something about men welcome to the party man. We don't do that shit here
Well, where are you from? I am live streaming right now, and I'm listening to the fucking shit
We don't do that shit man. Okay good. I like this guy. I like this guy already Alex
This is a new friend of the show
We need some new blood see like it as soon as we get rid of those guys a new blood comes in like a good guy
We traded to the right time for a are you what are you Spanish or?
Are you white me? No, I'm not God people say I'm Mexican Spanish. No, I'm not I'm not I'm white American all the way
Okay
well
Yeah, well, how'd you find the show or who do you know anybody in the community or?
Mostly through Goddy and JT. They're
Sort of enemies of mine, but they have encouraged me to come in here for
More attempts than I can count
well that's scary got in JT sent you that's scary
No, God those are all boys those are actually our people we love them got in JT so
Are you a part of CFF or no, this is just
Okay, you're gonna look you're right reminds me of like the grumple still skin uh
You know what I'm saying?
dog I can't really see
Somebody came up here before and they post the cock out, you know
A day come on my stream and pull their dicks out. I never let them on camera
Shut the fuck up. He won't he won't I like this guy Alex. He's gonna be a good guy. So
So, how are you so, um
Do you have you heard of me before or seen me before or yes, I've known about you for
Approximately a year. I've kind of avoided this place due to
Association with certain people
My trauma in here. I'm gonna drag my bullshit in here
I
Bullshit city drag it in drag it in you've been watching for no, no, this is not bullshit
It's off the door, buddy. I mean bullshit city. I mean like fun city like you can bring your bullshit here
Well, welcome it. No, I don't have any work it out with you
I don't have any bullshit shut the fun anybody else in the community like you know do summer, you know
He's laid back. I like laid back. Nobody tells me shut the fuck up the first night. They meet me see this guy
I like
I'm right in the right right right area or no Midwest. Let me turn the I need to turn my audio receiver
Also, I can hear this a bit more clearly. I'm wasted tonight. I'll tell you that you're wasted. Okay, perfect
Oh, yeah, I am I'm drinking some uh, every night
You receive these things for good shit
B-Box 11.1% alcohol by volume. Those are expensive voodoo ranges like
47.1 oh
That's strong
Well, I'm strong
Yeah, both ideas party punch. I didn't even I didn't eat very much today. So, you know, I have it
I do have a new website, you know, I know you McDonald's tonight. By the way, I told you Sunday. Oh
My lucky night. Maybe you can look for breakfast. Good morning. I guess so if we make it. Oh, it's that it is breakfast time
Six forty seven, so it's five forty seven four twenty three. It doesn't open
Forty seven here. Yeah, I think McDonald's opens here like four or five. I think it's six forty seven here
Yeah, I do not
Maybe five six eight nine
Well, how did you have a channel or do you um, you said you're a streamer, right?
My stream is mostly dead. I have no pretty much nobody who comes in there. I
Do I don't think that's about oh, well, you learned in the right place my friend psych you'll help you with that
I talk about Tesla. That's pretty much it. I slept. Okay. Well, Tesla is interesting. I mean, you know what?
I like I like Grock Tesla not Tesla
Sorry, I miss an auntie it did
Tessa
Tessa. Yes, you probably know her. I'm sure 60 people heard know that name. I know Tessa
You're not talking about olive oil run
Yeah, I'll run test the violet. Have you heard of test the violet? That's only no no he laughs
My cousin my wife
I'm talking about my wife, man. Oh, okay. Is she a streamer or she's known in the community? No, she's uh,
She's a bitch. Oh my god. Okay, so
She's pissed off for you that
That's a bitch
Huge one. Oh my god
Is she in a secret society?
Is she in Eastern Star?
No, she knows your channel.
She is the reason I know of this channel.
Oh, okay.
Because she's been in here.
She never like it.
The Plot Dickens, the Plot Dickens.
Yeah.
Is she someone that watches the show regularly or?
Regularly would be like at least two years that I know of.
You look so familiar though.
the
I'm not playing this since I was fucking like fucking eight or nine. Don't give me that.
Are you stalking Tessa? Because Sadie starts, he says you're her stalker, lol.
He has a little bit, but she stalks me
He said yes a little bit
You know you stoke the bitch you can't either you can't stoke so I'm like what what guy is not in love with the woman
Does not stalk her a little bit
100%
But who is testing? Is she worth stalking? I want to see her now. Show me a picture of her. Is she beautiful?
Tessa. Are you the guy that asked her to pig him?
I've run pictures of her on my channel, I've had her edited pictures of her up that are masturbating, everything else.
Don't even start being on that man, shut the fuck up.
No, the sketch you started on then, hold on.
Just rewind it a little bit.
Emma?
Yeah.
He's not talking about Emma Leviathan. Is he that's a city said yes, I guess I guessed it
No, I am open and honest about everything. She's passed out pictures. She mine dogs is out there
See everybody knows my address my name my full name
Levi isn't I have no a fucking idea what you're talking about
Doesn't know Emma, but no, it's a home Sadie Sadie. How do I know Sadie though?
I know Sadie in the chat Sadie sarsie. No, but I heard has to be for I know that name
I've heard it. I've seen her. I know who he's talking about. I just can't place the
Goddier JT would be who you know that name from okay, okay
Tessa Tessa Tessa. I know that name
Lord Vader yes, I know Vader and he's a douche bag. Yeah, that's true
What's what's them rain, you know rain I
Know rain. I that's JT's
Do you know Ziggy wife girlfriend? I don't really know at this point
Ziggy yes I know him he comes on my panel now and then how about who's that who's that southern guy I'm Alex
Who's that got the big southern accent that always?
Hi, Ryan Ryan Ray Ray one ray that ray. Yeah, exactly
He's never come on my panel, but I know him. I don't think there's no point
Okay, yeah
And that's the other guy
Honorary CFF
I'm like, you know, they gave me some they gave me an honorary pay a pair of monkey wings
Oh, they made me the president by the way, you were sleeping when I say
Dating rain. I took all the CFO. Hey
They made me
Dead and buried man
Hey, don't go away about chat friends forever
Yeah, I do you know that are you the chat forever? No, it is chat funeral forever. Oh
CFF stands for chat funeral forever
Oh
Right about that, but I'm just mocking it a little little bit. He's making fun of me. He's making money
Have you ever been with a man
They almost called it up
Give me that shit, man. I'm not I said no fucking allegations about me being buying gay
That's kind of gay a little bit. I mean, he's like you look okay. I mean you can't blame them and I thought you were gay
That's why you're here
Oh my god
If you like it dude in the ass man
Woman in the ass don't don't give me that shit
Oh, you know
He said you never lived, huh? You know tight the ass all this room you come in like two seconds damn tight
Yeah, I like the pussy tight I still is the way to go
Fucking a bunch like a plunger
Crazy
Just trying to start the comedy a cock like
Shut the fuck up man, shut the fuck up, shut the fuck up, shut the fuck up, shut the fuck up, shut the fuck up, shut the fuck up man, shut the fuck up man, shut the fuck up man, shut the fuck up man, shut the fuck up man, shut the fuck up man, shut the fuck up man, shut the fuck up man, shut the fuck up man, shut the fuck up man, shut the fuck up man, shut the fuck up man, shut the fuck up man, shut the fuck up man, shut the fuck up man, shut the fuck up man, shut the fuck up man, shut the fuck up man, shut the fuck up man, shut the fuck up man, shut the fuck up man, shut the fuck up man, shut the fuck up man, shut the fuck up man, shut the fuck up man, shut the fuck up man, shut the fuck up man, shut the fuck up man, shut the fuck up man, shut the fuck up man, shut the fuck up man, shut the fuck up man,
And I you know like that little tampon debris that oh wow
If you fuck a girl in the air, so you gay because basically you're fucking an asshole
Which a man has so you can fuck a man in the air. So it's good. You know sex you you might be a
It is a vagina I never told her that
Yeah, if you like anal with a woman you basically like you know, I'm with anyone all the way because they know they know
No, but it's but a girl they know it's no different than a man's anal. It's just a butthole
Oh my god
I'm not talking about the pussy dick. I'm talking about the asshole
If you can fuck a bitch in the ass, you can fuck a man in the ass, right?
Do you know flirty diamonds? Have you heard of flirty diamonds?
No, I've not heard that man. Okay. Well, she's a beautiful beautiful woman. You might like her instead of
No, I have no interest. I had no sex once am I gay?
No, no, yes, you're gay. No. Thank you psych
Jesus
But I mean does that make me gay cuz I fucked an asshole
No, we got bigger fish to pry poison as a wrench to fuck
I'm kidding. I'm sharing poison sharing porn of sick and I'm full. So I have to like, you know, have poison
that I'm a wrench to pat two hours ago in the
All the wheel runners babies. Oh, sorry man. I will run is man hating spoil girl who wants on dr. Phil
By the way, I will run loves me. Okay. Go say the name Alexander McQueen to her and that bitch will die
So what's your I used to be a monitor a channel site. I've been around the block
But why did you why'd you get I know all about Tessie and Claire? I
Know all of my little Claire
I live or run see there. That's my girl. I love that crazy bitch and she loves me
But we had a falling out we had a falling out one night with Emma
But then it's like, you know, I get accused of stalking Emma because I went to her chat like three times after I got unmodded
I mean, it's like so ridiculous. I'm getting accused of being a spiritual trafficker. No, you know what a spiritual trafficker is
I'm trying to figure it out
Have you heard of that term
No, I had to turn my volume down here. I can't hear shit too well. Are you are you aware of a porn starting?
Yeah, play me Tassie. I love her sake tits play me Tassie. I love him
Play me. Yeah, bro. You came a little sake tits. I love it with your body
Skinny and with a sake tits and a pussy's pink
I'll fuck the shit out of all of all of all run. I don't go fuck if she looks like all of all
She's funny with that
Literally looks like all of all from pop-up. That's why she calls herself that isn't it?
We go we go we go we go we go
I'm sure she does
100% she knows who you are
a million percent out of all of us
I feel like from a year ago
Ty Blades used to be obsessed with her
and share her but I thought she was kind of scary
cause you talk about like
she has all the accounts
she's probably up here at Sadie Starseed right now
I'm selling all these panels
I wouldn't be surprised
he may be on to something there
he does have more accounts
Comprehend me 100% I catch you sometimes. I'm like all of Halloween unless you with your stupid old
She's everywhere that girl. You know Lisa Jordana. I'm friends with her
Here she is
Dude your cap of mine act quite well here. You know who Lisa Jordana is
I'm capping your ear. Oh, I love her too. Alisa with her yellow eyes. She's been live lately
She has little duck lips
So that's only slow man. The poorly Alisa she doesn't need something man equal, but no one could be with that cycle
She's too crazy. I don't think she's really talking about the same person
Yeah
Keep up with the cycles here
I'll have all run to she needs a good name too, but they're crazy. What man could be a lot of oil and one man could be well
Lisa think about it. I'm not a special guy to be with those girls last night. I'm not out of that that out of it
He's out of it. Oh my God. He's so drunk. She's online constantly and hates men. I'm a real person next. So Sadie's a real person
I guess Tessa hates men. Is she lesbian or just hates men except for like I have suspected
She is strongly lesbian, but
Closeted I'll just say that
closeted
Well, I mean aren't women all kind of by bisexual at least or or not in love eating pussy
You know, I've been with those ones out there, you know, they'll kiss a girl
Kind of tickle you a little bit
Tickle tickle your ass. Don't eat bush. Don't eat bush, but bush can't get them pregnant and at the end of the day
They have eggs that drop and they don't need a baby
Biologically, they want a baby, but they don't want to be a man. They want like, you know, I think they women would be fine
Correct. They want a bush that can impregnate them like a and then welcome to life. Yeah, this guy is
Guys onto it. No, no
They milk men for their semen and their jokes, right?
Exactly women are evil. They use men. We are hunters and gatherers. They need us to do that task
It's not bad. I'm not saying I'm not judging or anything. I mean, I love women. I love women
I mean a few of them
You know, I this show is 90% men. I don't know and I'm a gay guy
I would think that I would have it like a but women don't seem to like
Jamie like Jamie likes me and this Sadie woman and I think they're the only way you're a gay guy. Yeah, I'm gay
Okay, and you know no no dude. I do not judge. I have no issue with that. Don't get me wrong
Okay, but I'm not I'm not
Despite what people say
I don't think he's gay. He's in love with two girls for being gay
He's in love with this girl Bita and the other one Alexander. He's in love with
But net so that's like kind of barking up the wrong tree though because lesbians are not really like
Into man right
Like hardcore lesbians usually like you know
Kind of like they emulate men a little bit, but usually they I
Mean I'll buy out a little little bit. I mean the farthest I will go is I will DP double penetrate
No, I will not go any further than that. I'm not gonna so you're saying like you would you
That's the sport you can go D.P. This guy's like I won't go further than that
You don't have further than that. You're in a circus act. Well ten cocks in your ass. So what do you mean?
I can't do that man. I can't be fucking a girl and some guy fucking her in the ass while I'm fucking her in the pussy like that's
That's gay
We have a disagreement there because I will go that far, but I will not go any further
Well, that's a fact that you have I guess everyone has fantasies, you know, I respect that whatever
No, I like to please my woman is all it's about
She likes to I'll give her to
all day you high-five buddy
exactly whoo double high-five
I'm not focused on the other guy I'm focused on what's wrapped around me
I'm focused on her it's a perfect match
double high-five it was a joke double penetration get it double high-five
I know it's a joke man don't take it too personally
I know I don't mean to be weird this is the way so this is a tarot channel
but it's probably like the weirdest tarot channel on YouTube
um we're
Basically, instead of tarot, I'd rather double penetrate with you.
Oh, good morning, reality answers.
See, reality answers is another female panel.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
This guy, women, close your ears.
I'm trying.
I have always had an interest in tarot, like the cards and shit
like that.
You're not, like, spiritually or ritualistically.
But, oh, well, you haven't got a reading from Psyche.
Who changed that?
Don't give me a reason right now.
And you ask me a holy cake.
I don't see no meat so well.
I don't even need a card for you.
All I can say is, in your future,
I see our cocks rubbing together.
How about that?
OK, we're far off here.
I told you it was good. See this guy's magic. He knows what he's doing
To card in the deck man, that's all that is
Okay, well, you don't have to I believe in do any means but I don't believe
I think I lost him Alex. Hello. I'm here. I hear you. Hello. Hello. Yeah, Alex, can you say sorry to
Amber, Alex, please? Sorry, Amber. Alex, please. There you go. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you. You know, you did go a little far. Okay, so we have Mud Shark Mondays in the backstage.
Do we want Mud Shark Mondays? Sorry, Amber.
the
I would calibrate all the time.
I'm picking the paper towels.
Tricks don't.
Hey, Amber, look at, Amber,
I think I made a boyfriend tonight.
Glaze.
Don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't.
Do you see that?
I've been glazed and I hear his boyfriend, see?
Don't, don't do this shit, man.
He's willing to do it like that.
My man has a woman, Tessa.
I don't know, do you know Tessa?
You're gonna bring me unwanted fame.
I won't, no, oh please, come on.
My life is infamy come on
My life is shit. Trust me, man. I'm
Well, it's not it's now that you met me is gonna get a lot better
You might get you might have no I've been seriously considered and killing myself for a long time now
Oh, don't say that. I mean I've had enough of this SUIC ID talk to that. No, I know I understand that and trust me
It does not go that far, but Monica Foster
No, I do not know that person. She's like the basically the black Jenna Jamison. She's she's she's she's all she does Bible studies on YouTube
No, I don't know any of that I'm kind of out of this circle here. I know you through other people. That's about it
Okay, don't say that
But I was actually saying don't say that
You know my like a horse there see fun psyches funny, bro
Yeah, I know well Monica Foster or Alexander Mayer. She's very beautiful. Jesus. She's a she's crazy as a
You know, two to three dollar bill. That's right
Shit, I was right my man. You can say just let it out all the lot
Do you hate that's one crazy bitch? He's nowhere near the caliber. Does anybody know this test of women?
He likes his woman named Tessa.
I think that's the only one.
Dude, you all know her.
I know that because I know you through her.
All of you through her.
OK.
Wow.
This is my girlfriend that person I've been involved with for fucking years.
Alex said she was.
Five years now.
Her name is Tessie.
Is it Tessie or Tessa?
T-E-S-S-A.
T-E-S-S-S-A.
I thought you said Tesla and I thought you said you liked it. No
Not Tesla. I'm anybody did tonight. So I'm kind of slowly my
Do you want to get in a Tesla with me and hello? What's going on?
Alex a Arthur. I'm gonna I'm gonna have sex. Whoa, what without me. No, you can come too
,
you want to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to be
Yes, talk to Alice for that. I'm gonna find that's all I was trying to ask you earlier Alex
I'm gonna ask you dude when you get pissed off. Can you control your anger more bro?
Cuz you know, I can't I can't at the moment
You start doxing me like what the shit how can I talk to you all about dude come on, bro?
And your name is Austin.
He said he wants to talk to you.
Oh, my God, here we go.
Oh, I know, pal.
Thank you, in Tessa.
Yeah, but why do you have to mention that?
It's Daniel Allen.
Daniel Allen, Potato Chips, and Arthur.
Oh, my God, here we go.
How's that sound?
Registor is calling me a F-A-G-G-O-T.
Doc.
Dude, why do you have to do that shit, though, bro?
Me?
Like, we're not cool, and you started, like, talking shit.
Like, come on, bro.
Look at him crying with his fucking shoulders and golden legs.
Are we not don't listen to Harry like man this first I'm glazed. Hmm. Hello. Are we not cool?
No, we're not cool. Of course. We're not cool. I'm only cool with psyche assholes
Nobody up here with psyche you retard. You don't know that. I don't know any
Yeah, I'm not going you amber be the fucking anyone. Okay. All right
You are my sworn enemy in my eye. Okay
Thank you's my brother my family. I'm here for him. You can go eat shit and die. I could give a fuck about you, bro
Wow, okay
I don't give a fuck what happens to you in life later boy. I'm here for psyche my man
What I think about him
The whole track will go in shit and die
Everybody on this panel could go in shit and die besides like you and me in my I was unaware
Remember that well now you're aware asshole. What is the fuck up? We're talking shut the fuck you fucking loser shut up
Go in shit and die potato chip boy
You're just scared away that this guy and I like him
No, you're not going to scare me.
Fucking eat shit and die glaze welcome. You're still talking
You don't even
Don't ever say this nigga you little white
Shut the fuck up
I was fucking slapped shit out of you, bitch-ass boy.
A few minutes ago, you thought I was Mexican.
Shut the fuck up.
No, I mean, I like Latin guys, but I don't care what you are.
You're a human being, right?
I like Latin women.
I'll tell you that.
Well, let's have a fiesta.
Open my heart listen to this dumb bitch in the chat. Oh, I'm there amber wrench
You don't hooker bitch amber you can eat kid and I do
No, I'm just believe right now that you guys told me we were friends or something. Oh, let's think it's
I'm only here for psyche you morons
All of you can eat shit, suck my dick and die.
Oh my god, Alex, Alex, come on.
Wow, my crap.
Alex, that's too far.
Clearly he cares about your channel, huh?
Alex, no, that's not good, Alex.
No, no, no.
Wow.
Weirdo!
I can't find the clip where Alex and I were in the bushes,
but I didn't need to do it.
Glaze, are you there?
Dada, I almost need to go and puke.
Hey, yo, what's up Tessa? I'm not into Roman showers. I'm sorry
You know, that's what they're called to the weirdo on the panel. What's up?
By weirdo, you mean me. Yeah. Yeah, you what's up? Yeah, what's going on?
He's weird because what's he what's the screen name? I can't see the channel right now. I can't see well
I'm drunk and I can read your name
Not help, but I'm driving. I can't see the screen. What's your name?
I'm driving drunk, and I can still read your name
You can pick me up, please
I don't care I got a date
I'm asking so I could talk to him his name is glaze glaze. All right ladies. Thank you. Fuck sorry
What do you want to know? What's up, glaze? I think I've heard you on other channels on other panels, you know about a CT, right?
CT no, I've never been there. Hey y'all the truth
No
Okay, it's your the wrong person. All right. You you probably know me through other people, but
You know about Zaya
No, do you know about Sam and Sam and yes, but I've never been there
45 and like the
Do you know IP to IP to yes that that that's where I know that name from you know, do you know Banny Blanco?
No, okay, although you don't know about I know you know big Vicky Victoria
and
playing mate Tessie or what are you doing?
Yeah, playing mate Tessie.
I'm the one who won, what about her?
What, you like her?
Yeah, he's obsessed with her, he's a stalker.
I love her, what about her?
This is pretty high, I ain't going to lie.
There you go.
The one you're talking about is probably my girlfriend.
Your girlfriend?
She has a lot of accounts and plays these games, so I do not really know how far it goes.
we have an open relationship, so I'd not particularly invest in what you guys do together
Does she know you guys are a thing?
I do not even know if this is the same person, so I do not
There's only one playmate hessie in the world. Yeah, exactly. Exactly. She makes children cancel raked. That bitch is how she's my she's my baby
He's meeting up in a girl version.
All aboard running me in a female version.
Of course, I'm getting that shit in ways you don't not comprehend.
He doesn't give a fuck about losers.
Band cake later.
Permaband, permaband.
Just like I don't give a shit about you.
He doesn't give a fuck about nobody.
You got cancer, LOL.
I'm gonna look up. I'm gonna look at the best thing that ever happened in this world like me. Is it playmate?
Yes, that's dude. You guys are frying my fucking brain
Welcome to the chaotic you found the road. This place is
We all need a bit of chaos in our lives. Don't we do you know about
You and me. I'm looking at her right now. Oh, yes, he is
do what now so yeah I didn't playmate Tessie is he a playmate is he in playboy I know some playmates
No, you're talking about something someone else. I I do not know what the fuck you're talking about
Yeah, Alice is a bunch of naked women on the in the Google. No
Twice somebody said in the chat. Who's the reader that said I was here twice
The one I'm talking about
My founder I founder is it this woman? Hold on this woman
Perm absolutely if it was okay, I'll get I'll get I just gonna show her one second
I just need to save the picture home
JPG is it this woman right here, and you have to we will confirm or deny and it is this woman
Oh shit, let me see
image
desktop
Okay, is it this
Is it her as your profile photo that's easy bro. No, no
That's all the boy run my peeps
that is not the test I know
I've had her
No, that's not that's not
that's not that's not that's not
Tessie appeared on dr. Phil where she was first posted to games against her father, and then it says
So that bitch chose to kiss and pussy
Fucking bro. Go to all me fans. You'll see that bitch is spreading her pussy and her tits naked. He's also
Not do that
it says I heard yeah I got
pictures I got videos over
spreading our pussy yourself
for her literally shared on
discord bro okay you know I
don't have to it's public
Just go to her channel and all her links and it'll take you to fensley not even only fans
There's a thing called fensley if you go to fensley and look over all over right now
Play me Tassie on fensley and you subscribe. You'll see that bitch fucking shoving cock in her
Oh, she's into taggy little kids. She's got the staggiest little kids. I was so fucking
No, no
You know why she calls herself olive oil run because she looks like all of all from Popeye
Papa
She literally looks exactly like that bitch
And she's on fancy bro spreading her pussy lips and her tits and her asshole that bitch is a whore
That's why
Then you may find a timer for showing a little pee and she knows who I am this I mean that's kind of scary because she's beautiful
Yeah, that bitch is crazy. She knows who everybody is
Around forever and she's insane. All right, shut the fuck up psych. Do you know should open up in only fans?
What are only fans? Do you know who should open up in only fans account me sing at this point?
Oh, please nobody wants to see that every like a fetish for like a
Man with a vagina his username should be only chowed. Oh
Yeah
Titles dedicated to her like you do like people making fun of you about her
She's a genius.
They show you her whole that story.
Her dad sucked in lips up.
Shut the fuck up, man.
So what are you?
So guys, guys, guys, there's a video of her dad calling her out.
Her dad is on the bitch on live panel.
Don't know.
He's like, nobody cares about you.
Oh, God.
You're staying on.
Yeah.
You can sleep with olive oil run real deep.
Who I am.
Olive oil run nose.
Yeah.
But be careful.
That bitch too.
That bitch is crazy.
Yo, just take into her lookup of
playmate Tassie on Google. I
don't want to run. And you're
going to see her own father made
a panel cursing her out. Like
this bitch sucked. Yo, she does
nothing. Her dad supports her.
But she lives with her dad, her mom abandoned her and the dad and she comes and gives them
money because the mom they're paid.
Her parents are paid.
Is this guy still talking?
You know, this is why you could use me here in Texas with two paid as parents and she
goes all the way around.
Look into it.
It gets crazy with that bitch.
This guy is still talking.
Yeah, I'm still talking. What about it?
Now he's going to a rage
Painted hair
Don't fuck up or we're here for psyche not all of them as you live in New York with me easy less
We'll find you and fuck you up
That's a threat
a hundred percent we'll find you tomorrow your house roll up and be
okay that's a threat psyche come on really donalds please and uh stop making threats against arthur
please he's not saying he's fucking threatening i don't know he's always crashing out us like and
he's getting mad at me for like doing a decision on my alex what's wrong stop it calm down
Damn what a weirdo
Yes, you're seriously out today. I barely know you shut the fuck up man. Oh
Oh shit up in front of his house in front of his family. Whoa, what the fuck? Okay, Alex, you know put it at your boy
Yo, that's weird
This is why I'm leaving New York soon, brother. Thank God. I don't know
I mean, it's like I'm trying to talk to this guy and then it's like I can't get in
I mean it's like Alex Alex you're saying stuff against to us. I mean, it's just can you stop it?
I mean, he doesn't care, bro. He doesn't care. Can you just calm down, please? We're trying to have a conversation. I mean, Jesus
Calm down I
Read people's panels pretty well and I
I don't go overboard and I do not cross the line.
Hey, do you know a guy named Blade?
Yes.
From Texas?
Like, he's like kind of like, maybe he's got like a stub.
He was, I met him at Benny's.
He was obsessed with Benny.
Alex wants me all to himself.
I know Alex, but he said he's went into double penetration,
so we can do together.
Go for it, dude.
You, me, and Alex?
oh hell yeah go for it okay Alex he's in hey I do not judge you're gonna be
there right oh no I'm not getting into this shit but I do not judge why don't
you are aware that psyche is gay I don't know if you know that
yes I'm I'm very well aware but I like I said I do not judge I'm not gonna but
what is this one but so what does olive oil think about me or Tessie or
whatever the fuck her name what does she think she thinks you're pretty
entertaining she likes your tarot card reading why she's come to the show have
I talked to her before you know she's been in the chat
I don't know. I don't know.
I'm out of it tonight. I'm back in out of here. Yeah
I'll take care
She's so racist is the funniest thing she's so funny
Alex, way to go, Alex, random panelist Alex, way to go.
Stop talking, why are you still talking?
It's okay.
Why is he talking over you, site?
I don't know.
This guy doesn't respect you.
He doesn't even listen.
He doesn't respect you.
If that thinks this is his channel.
You're a piece of shit, shut the fuck up.
Who's the one that used to come up here every day and take them down? I'm gonna put a this in your head Christine
I'm gonna put this and this and this dude you just threatened me right now. What the fuck are you talking about?
That you are piece of shit, and you're here sucking psyche's dick, but you were actually trying to take him down a few months ago
That's breaking TOS isn't that trying to take him down breaking TOS what that saying I'm gonna sign on and break your fucking face
What the fuck I don't know I mean he's trying to my god
Like why is he doing that?
I really don't get it. I don't know.
I don't get it.
Alex, why are you doing that?
Like, first of all, I was trying to talk to this guy
and you're screaming nonsense.
It was working out.
And then you're threatening and...
Yeah, like he literally runs off new people every time Alex and then you're but you're mad about singing through your glow
All they did was show their vaginas on this and then he's mad. He's asked you so inquires. They're never new people here
Yeah, they're all scared of you. You just you run away. He runs them off. What's wrong with you Alex?
Well, because my man does it over my ass cheeks. I get jealous
My territorial into anal sex
Okay, I'm sorry
Those cheeks of mine you're mine only my man
Yeah, well I get jealous man I get jealous on my baby
Her cat's my man.
Her cat's not like her.
That's my man.
Yeah, that's my man.
My cats love me.
Wow, well, you know that shit's getting clipped.
You're concerning Jamie's Cowboys, Alex.
I hope it is.
And share it with the world.
That's my man.
Clip it again.
Alex, your man is getting hungry for some Mickey D's.
Can I get a couple of copies and maybe a,
what's it called, the McRiddle?
Please then he stayed quiet. I shut him up. Finally. Oh
I'm doing the math in my head like hold on to coffee. Okay, it was claiming you like that's my baby
That's my boo, and then he's like, hey, I mean Alex. He said double so you can both have it
I heard a double double toil in trouble fucking weirdo, bro. What a fucking weirdo. I
Would wipe the floor with him
When now you're threatening no like I would wash the floors with him, you know, okay like you know mop mop the month
Yes
Can you, can you come up, my floor, my kitchen floor needs to be lost.
What's wrong with it? Is it wet and slippery?
Wow, you like the floor to me. That was my feeling.
Seriously, that's messed up, man. I don't why would you let him say that to me psyche? I'm hurt
I gotta kick him out
No, thank you stay with you little floor wax you little my oh you both are waxing floor waxer
Oh my god, you scared now. He's scared away Alex. No, no, no, Alex join. I'll leave I'll leave
Well, uh, well, no, I'm all alone again
This is not what I wanted.
I wanted all of them at the same time.
This is not right.
Yeah, Alex, fish taco or something.
You know, I think, now I have to stay until,
I don't know, guys, I'm so horny.
I'm just kidding, I'm not really.
Hey, who's coming up to the show?
Hello.
Hi, how are you?
I think your camera froze.
Hello.
Are you making that face of me lady?
You're scaring me
Hello
No, that was that was weird. That was a weird. Yeah, hi. It's me Jesus
I
Don't know guys guys. Why don't I have the weirdest life?
like
Yeah, playmate all of so no seriously
She's told this guy for over a year about me.
I watched this woman, you know, in, like, afraid
that she'd know who I was, and she was recommending me.
What's going on here?
Am I being punked?
I'm almost, I'm two steps away from a DP scene
with her stalker.
This is great.
She's so as I as well. I can I can do that too
Maybe
Narcissistic she paid money for her daughters. She birthed that she birthed
She she gave birth to cats. Hold on. They always hide her hold on. I'm an Alexander level stalker. Well, that's
But you know, I but I get called the stalker though
Why am I why do I get it called? Why do I get called stalker by women that are stalking everybody?
So I can't even like really they're more likely to have a car to like stalk me
Can she take can she come pick me up?
Hello
Meet you for those shit
Hmm
Okay, well, let's see was oh guys. Well guys. I added a guy's I was able to add like a lot more stuff to that website
While we're doing
So let's see what else we got on. Oh my god. There's porno on the screen. Oh, it's not just researching her name
Don't search the word playmate, please
I'm about to so guys you want to see my website?
Just it's actually in the description of the show it's called cult codex dot me
And I will share you the screen. I mean, I mean, it's hard. I don't know. I don't want to scare
Yo, yo clumsy she got clipped for picking them up by the oh, hold on her cats
Well, you can pick your cat like what I do is I pick my cats up from the armpits
But I like you know have my fingers like that. So it's like you're not it's not uncomfortable
problems you home for the cat around
tricks
here
tricksy tricks will only come up. I call another cat because then he
You know, he's kind of like your little jealous guy. Hey. Oh my god, and
Lola came in chewing up a mouse
Okay, well
Are we interested in seeing
What website? Oh, it's looking the look in the title of the show Colt codex.me. I'll share the screen
So this website is my
Magnum opus it includes every all my 1,173 episodes
All 293 people in my show, 459 lower entries, 489 quotes,
502 topics, you can go in.
You can go to episodes like this, pick a run at random.
Psyche Awakens 152, see, there I am.
Let's see what's on this one.
Oh, there's Lola.
What are you doing? Hold on one second.
Can you sing me a buddy moment?
Can you just pick me up?
And that.
Lola.
Lola, what happened with you?
Oh.
And she loves the kids.
She loves the kids.
Look how good I look.
So healthy.
She raised all the kids and all the kids are healthy.
All the kids are healthy.
You're going to pop up and show your J-poppers?
That's not your dick, because I've already seen Sagan,
300 Glows dick tonight.
And we're going to give it a little bit of a sprain
if she were ever here to see other kids.
Oh.
You're going to make her loads and loads.
Why is it so choppy?
When the kid was born, that was the first time in her life, and then she's in her life, right?
We love Lola.
We love you, Lola.
You're a true happy cat too.
What am I doing?
The camera wasn't in the chat, we love Lola.
Why is my stomach like mini mansons right now?
It's a mini I got pictures of many Manson
Like that
There's a little P a really good day
No, he showed him and stick having sex on the phone. Oh
Oh, it's rude, okay
Yeah, Tony sent me pictures of mini Manson like
P and his bladder or yeah
And he looks pregnant literally
He's pulling a microphone or something or
Why am I so drunk my
Good morning, just
She's happy I mean she of course she's happy here
Oh, there's magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic
I have Elisa, they spelled it wrong.
It says another streamer that's psyche supports.
Currently has a friend, Eric, visiting from out of town.
Everyone remember Eric from Elisa Jordana?
We have Bea, Bea's kitties.
Beebees kitties, Persian regular guests
who appears frequently known for spicy personality
and cooking.
You know what I like?
I like putting lentils in some like oil.
I don't know what she said.
Look, they say her name is B.
Her name's not B.
B, this, I like this one, Beaches.
Fellow streamer who joined late in the stream
received it for supportive readings and encouragement.
So I have 13 pages of guests so far.
Pretty cool, right?
Look at how many betas I have.
I have like pages of beta, beta va, beta,
Benny Brad, beta va, frequent panel participant
who appears intoxicated and has an accidental camera incident.
Oh, I want to see that one.
That was this one. Oh my god, the best
There's Michael again
Created them and it's like it's like your father is your father gonna like say
Oh, I don't want the best for my son or my daughter
You know the father is gonna like want to bring the best their children
Okay, so it's kind of like he's more in the
Medium like the middle of the gods and the humans, but he did create the humans and stuff like that, right?
So that's from atheists and he's punished and you know, but
Basically, he was Prometheus, also called Leia for sometimes, he's like, you know, also like this light, the fire, the light, okay?
So, he has some different names and stuff like that, but
just, but I'm, but at the end of the day, I'm a human.
Hey, Sadie, love you! Hey, Sadie, come back!
I'm a fire to this higher self and everything, I'm not gonna say I'm God or anything, or I'm a God, or I'm gonna say I'm a human being,
just like everybody else, but I think we all have this higher light in ourselves, right?
great well well I'll say but we'll see about angels like angels are more of
like God's messengers so angels kind of have the will of God and then demons
Maybe the children of they're so related to God and stuff like that
But they're like more attached to the material and so human beings are kind of the middle or like angels and demons, right?
Maybe I'm not explaining it right, but that's that's how I explain it. It's like we're
Higher and a lower, right? We can choose the higher and the lower path, right?
We have the choice because we have free will because God really wanted human beings to be able to have their own free will
Make the choice. Here's for the choices are we gonna go through the higher or the lower?
We can say through the lower, right, but we'll be in hell, right?
You can you can aspire to the higher we can ascend. Okay, so I hope I'm not I hope I'm not explaining it wrong
Yo, what up psyche? What's up? How are you doing? I'm doing good. I'm doing good
You can continue playing that video. Okay. I mean, I was like, I mean, I just think I started this website
It's gonna have every single guess that appear on the show like in their quotes and stuff like that and then like the episodes
They were on
Don't know if this was when beta had like the it said she she appeared intoxicated and had a camera slip
I'm not sure if this was the right episode. Oh
You talking about the
Bush, yeah, but you can't really see anything. It was kind of like, you know
Kind of course, of course. Can you see into a bush? Can you see a cat through a bush outside?
Um, that I saw I actually found some power rangers in my bushes and then I had to call the police
Okay, you think be the best power rangers in her bush. I wouldn't be surprised
I don't know, but I wouldn't be really much of a surprise anymore.
I just found out that Olive Oil Run been recommending my show for over a year.
I mean, this is another Playboy Playmate.
I mean, I know Playboy Playmates, I know at least like three or four.
But here's another one that I didn't even know I knew.
I mean, I know of her and stuff.
But, um...
They love you, Saiti.
They want your weenie
Yeah, I'm kind of scared because I all I heard is like I remember I watched
Olive oil runs show once and she was talking about like like like robbing men and stuff and I was kind of like oh my gosh
What's up, boo. Hey, what's up?
Yeah, cuz you got yours was packing big dog. Yo clumsy, please. I need your thoughts
Is in love with me
I'm over here. Hold on. Let me. Let me give my hall of fame poppers out the oven. You're quick. Hold on.
Oh, I love Sam, man.
Gio, Clumsie, Clumsie, Clumsie. Hold on.
You pulled your two front teeth and how old are you? You look pretty young.
Doesn't that shit happen when you're like 90?
I'm 36, but uh...
You know some keys that you're missing?
Listen, listen, listen!
What are you talking about for breakfast there, so?
Listen!
What a fucking stuff that, bro!
How do you feel about that?
Listen, you fucking piece of shit!
You have a mission to get back!
Listen!
Because this is my only golden life!
Listen, bro!
Shut the fuck up and listen!
That is great!
My two front teeth were never fucking real, you pendejo!
So you never had these is a little baby
Yeah, nigga, you got a problem with that or what?
Got a problem with that shit. Why don't you go? Hey, why don't you sit on fucking up?
Santa's fucking lap you fucking weirdo
Christmas time
Is going on this can't be real get away from me
Can you you don't brush your teeth and you've been doing drugs since you were
You over here on a motherfucker panel with no bitch
Yeah
You think me, miss, my teeth makes me
ain't a difference for me beating on your ass.
I want to sit in this lady's lap right here.
Cam up for us real quick, you fucking
catapilla eyebrow motherfucker.
Cam up real quick for us.
Samman, look at this, this lady recommended me.
Samman.
Other people to my show and she's famous.
She was on Dr. Phil.
Yo, wait, I was asking
Oh, what's up? What's up? Yo clumsy with what are your thoughts on Sam and bro, man? Who's that?
It's a guy that like makes you fall asleep and brings you good dreams.
Bro, I'm already past him, bro.
Nice.
It's your piece of shit.
It's your piece of shit, bro.
I'm done.
Nice.
Okay, that's cool.
That's cool.
Hey, but let him keep on clipping me because I don't do that.
I don't do that to him.
I'm just saying.
You don't see me in his chats.
You don't see me on his panel, but when I run my panel, I run my chats, I run my shit.
All right, so let me ask a fair question. Let me ask you a fair question
What are your thoughts on his brother having an account on you like for it's been years now? What a weirdo bro
How about if I told you this uh in the war dog days this was brother used to be on my dick
Why?
Like you like I never knew you have no teeth motherfucker
You know human can't open up bro. Oh my goodness go open that can't yo I will pop the corona thing block right between your teeth
Yo clumsy the human can open and I was no teeth at 36 years old, okay, that's a loser, bro
Go sell your cabinet your sunglass
Get a grand
You're never getting pussy for the rest of your life
You're never gonna touch pussy ever again
I got a fat wife. I got a fat wife. Oh
What a scumbag
Bro
I would beat Alex
You know, you got a little piece brother shut the fuck up with the hi-hats behind you go sell the house and get some
my boy
Life is over for you. Hold on. You need to like sound right, bro. I don't
I still got all my teeth.
I'm only missing two parts.
No, you know, smile for me.
No, you do not dick.
Your front teeth are missing. The most important teeth are missing.
You could be missing the back ones or something.
I'm over it. I'm over it too.
Are you mad?
Your whole front skin is gone, my boy.
Your knee sticks in your throat.
That is Crackhead City.
That means you saw Crack from sunrise to sunset, my man.
You're a scumbag, Alex.
It's people like this that that that that in reality, bro. They can't face reality. Like
I go like this on every store. I don't give a fuck. I still get told I'm I like no no too far
Oh, I'll fuck your bit like this nigga
I'll lick your be like this ball because you like gum jobs. You like gum jobs. He doesn't care about your
Job without scraping the park. I forgot. He's the devil. He doesn't care about you
This isn't that right, but you send that nigga money, right?
I'm right. He's your pin, bitch. Go send him some more money pussy. Yeah
Go send some more money pussy
No, you hungry tell him tell him baby
Yo, are you okay? You look really skinny, bro. You lost a lot of weight lady. Have you been eating?
Honestly, I just told you like raise your neck for me again
Yo, we got
Men's looks too much
Hey Alex, yeah, thank you. Don't flash your fake teeth. So we all know those are dentures. You have no teeth either
You've been doing math since you're 10. Those are fake teeth you fucking freak
Yo psyche are you think we're retarded?
This is the fakes keep on the planet
They're chopping up showing you fake teeth
You're not going back on until I get my McGrittle fucks
You're going Alex Alex might be mad because he got burned on some cope, bro. Leave him alone. It's okay
I think Alex wants to be
Hmm
Yeah, I know I mean it's like guys he's jealous because he heard about olive oil run
He's been like plugging my show for over a year and he's been
He was her mod and stuff like that, and she was nothing to do with me.
Psy-gay! Psy-gay!
It'd be like if Emma was like friends with him, and I'd be jealous, right?
Oh, I thought I asked them. I was asking Clumsy a couple of questions.
Okay, go ahead. You can talk to him one-on-one, I'll be right back.
Clumsy, just a minute. One more minute. One last question.
Clumsy, what are your thoughts on sick having the smallest penis in the community?
I heard about that. I heard that him and Aldi right now in a competition
Yo
Tell me tell me how
Sigg has Bush right. Oops. His fumes are longer than his fucking penis broke
what the fuck dude I asked psyche for a screenshot because I had a laugh bro I'm
sorry that's it in gay I'm sorry you I know I'm sorry you had to look at that
but goddamn was it that was it that bad yo you can barely see the tip all I see
is a fucking bush
I'm like, yo, is that his thumb?
What the fuck is going on?
Yo, I don't know what got into his head thinking
that'd be a good idea, bro.
That just sounds weird.
So it was like a thumb coming out of a bush, like, like that.
Like a homeless motherfucker coming out of where it's talking about, ain't no, you got a dolly?
The homeless guy's head is barely popping out. Oh
Say bro, I would never show face in the community
It's going on this can't be real get away from me. I don't understand any of this. Oh
I hope he's a, what do you call that shit?
I'm not a show or I'm a grower or something shit like that.
You better hope though.
You better hope.
What does he feel?
Yeah, I mean, oh my goodness.
I doubt it, bro.
At this point, what was that, you know what I mean?
I got a little peepie. What the fuck hold on hold on hold on hold on so so from what I heard earlier
Take poor mom psyche. Yes
Poor mom
Did you poor mom be there or she was just in the panel who else did you poor mom?
Good, Kate sent me the picture of his vagina from another show no vagina. Yeah, I mean, it's like I was fine
They're in like a hole you might want to say yes in any Audi
Yeah, it was an it wasn't any for sure. Well the way you put it. I'm not trying to sound fucking gay, bro
But it's like a head popping out of a fucking bush, bro. Like yeah, my god
I'm not trying to sound gay. All right, but I did some time so I've seen a lot of fucking
Wow
Wow, that's he has a little pee-pee, bro
Ain't that like uh, like a dysfunction like I don't know why I think it was a part of a humiliation
Ritual that he was forced to do
Do I don't even know how he jerks off at that little
That's crazy. That's crazy
I mean to be honest, bro
He kind of got a little bit of a good advantage if a chicks want to sit there and give him a chance because you know
No, this parameter and charge, you know nasty or nothing, but a girl's clitoris, bro
Is you know kind of like right there on top? It's mean you you know I'm saying yeah, so if he whatever whatever, you know, I mean
Yeah, you know what I'm saying
Advantage, but is it even that big?
it's just crazy bro. He might as well just let his hair grow out, shave the mustache, and just call himself Siggi.
And then, he put up a video of him bottoming for, um, for Siggi.
Yeah, I'll be right back.
Alright, big dawg.
What?
What did you say, Saiki? Hold on. What about a bottom? What?
Yeah, well 300 glow then he showed up his phone, uh-huh
He was having sex with sick sick was like sick was like rubbing the nub against his buck booty. Oh, no
He was like, oh, yeah, baby
Yeah, I won't allow it. Hey, Jamie. You have to tell me and
Jamie Jamie you just just hide them, you know, you're in charge
I'm a
But um, well, I yeah, how you been doing though. You've been doing all right. It's like I don't know. Well, you know
You know Alexandra is saying that you know
What she say today she said that
I'm like, uh, I'm she said I'm straight
She said, I'm a spiritual trafficker again.
She said, I'm a stalker.
She said, I'm working with Bita to do what?
Oh yeah, she said, I'm working with Bita to,
I don't really know what I'm working with Bita about.
I mean, before it was like,
I'm working with Samman and Bita on my wiki.
No, I run my wiki.
They're just they're just on my wiki wiki
Have you ever thought I'm just saying though and don't take this like too serious, but yeah, take it very light. Yes
Do you think honesty there might be a curse on you?
Well attempted, but I'm a better witch than they are so
Figure I ask that I mean cuz you know the women are very powerful like you know
Those those women are very powerful, but they have such bad intentions
Seems like I don't know. This is my
And I might I might get a lot of hate this but whatever but
To me Vita and Christine is using as like a rich
There what they're they're using you you're pretty much the ritual pretty much
Well, you know, I know that I mean I did I did like
Scribe into the ether and I saw them naked around a fire like sacrificing babies and stuff, but
I'm still more powerful
Hello
Know and it's like if you see if you see their boobs and stuff like that. It's scary like I haven't I have a better body
Didn't both of them put together I
Really do I'm gonna say some one thing once again
Oh my god, oh my god, I was just a joke. It was a joke. It was a joke. Christina was a joke
I'm so sorry. I'm sorry. He was it was a joke. I'm already about to tell you
No, it was not a joke. Like you don't joke like that. I am getting
Get off keep my name at your mouth. Oh, they don't talk to you
I don't talk about you, I don't talk to you, go suck SIGs pussy.
Fuck you bitch.
Psyche?
Stop talking about me.
I'm getting really tired of it, you've done this before with Crystal and now you're doing
it again.
That was a joke.
It was an obvious joke.
Don't joke that way.
What I tell you Psyche, don't joke that way.
Way the fuck go to sleep, bitch. Why don't you go to sleep? It's time for me to wake up
I'm a productive
Drunk, I'm a productive adult
Drunk I'll be there drunk
Beta don't really nearly like you drink. Oh, she don't know
No, she doesn't
But psych I'm telling you you need to make a public apology because I'm tired of this
Psych
Grind the ether and see you dancing naked around a fire. Okay. It was a joke. Well, but you know something I'm getting real tired of it
Who the fuck wants you that bitch naked around fire anyways, I'm sorry
Alexander loves Christine because Christina's
Well, that was awkward.
Okay, Christine, I am sorry.
Christine, I love you.
I really do.
Christine has nothing to do with,
I should have just said Bita and some other person.
I don't know, he put the words in my mouth.
Gosh, how embarrassing.
Oh my gosh, keep explaining what happened.
It was just a it was just a weird I
Don't know what comes out of my mouth. I'm it's okay. I mean, I'm just like just drinking like
It was stupid. I'm stupid. I don't think she's in it. I think
Christine basically knows
I like her I like I like her and I don't Christine
I thought that was like so ridiculous. I mean Chris with Christine said was these are um, these are be fun
But crystals that was ridiculous, but what I just said there was even like small ridiculous
So if I'm not gonna be apologetic for the next three months about that you just
I mean, I can't I'm sorry. I'm gonna all I can say I'm sorry. I was just a joke. It was like
Being sarcastic kinda, but it's okay, I'm sorry, but I am sorry
Guys I'm in trouble. Oh my god
Flumsies like oh you're cursed a drink am I drinking I'm drinking a beatbox pink lemonade
I'm sorry, I'm a little bit drunk. I'm a little bit drunk
But guys, I've been going through a lot lately too, you know, I've got like
I'm sorry. I don't, I don't want to, I don't want to hurt your feelings. It was, it was really kind of like,
so over the top, I didn't think that you'd take it too seriously. But it's okay. It's okay. I know
Alexandra thinks I'm a demon or whatever. I don't know. I mean, basically Satan incarnate when she's
Heck is going on. This can't be real. Get away from me. I don't understand any of this. I don't I don't
Finally I agree with KZ. You know KZ said about me terrible things. It's okay
It's not your fault. It's my fault. It's my fault
And Alex Alexander McQueen's mad at me because I mean everyone gets mad at me like you really
You're here. I want to hear her say to beta beta. You know what?
Sikes a good guy, you know lay off him a little bit. I would love to hear that Nick will I ever know
No
I'll hear bitching at me about beat it like oh my god. You said, you know
I mean beat his bunghole or something. I don't know. I don't know I'll always be in trouble. It's okay. I'll be the asshole
I'm the asshole. It's okay. It's okay
I'm used to it Emma
I don't know, probably other people, Alexandra, right?
I didn't mean to hurt anybody's feelings.
I don't think she, I don't think, I don't, I really, I really think she's a good person. I really think, like, I really think she's a good hearted person.
Like I said, she's a grandma. I, I respect grandmas. I respect women.
And I'm a jerk.
You know, you already heard I'm a spiritual trafficker.
You already heard I'm, you know, manipulating everybody.
It's me, guys, it was me the whole time.
Everyone thinks I'm this innocent.
No, no, actually nobody thought I was innocent.
Everyone thinks I'm guilty, but maybe I am innocent.
I'm really like Jesus.
I'm not like Jesus. I mean, I say I try to be like Jesus
Told you cheerleading Alice the other day was gonna backfire. Well. Oh, how about I told you so I told you so
Rg really I'm gonna make a cartoon about you next. Okay. Yeah, and I can do your voice. No, I can that was a wrong one
Yeah, I'm gonna do your voice. Yeah, I'm not doing it right right now. I had too much to drink. I'm sorry
Yeah, I
I'm gonna do pickles voice
Sweepie is for if you tell him 200 pounds
Actually, I played the clip of sweepie earlier tonight and she sounded totally a different person. I
Don't know but I need to I need to forgive sweepie even though she says
How disgusting he is how disgusting he is
Right, but I I'm apologizing trying to get her channel back, right?
Take the link we're cooking I'll cook you Sam and go over here
I'm sorry, I'm sorry clumsy, but I did I'm wrong right hey my fault, bro
Nobody's you know, I'm gonna be honest about something like like Christine Bros. He's always he's always bring me up man
About some bullshit, and I don't like that
Okay, well, I know I mean
I really don't care. I mean it's like actually I kind of like when like Alexander does a show about me
It means I'm relevant. So thank you Alexandra for the relevance. I mean
You got pumped. I don't know what god. I don't know what Christine's problem
I care that you see I'm straight finally my reputation is a little bit better
You know it but but think about think about this everything that she's just there and tells you about all the bad thing
He is doing how come she can't sit there and tell beat of that on her stream. Is she do it some wrong?
it's okay it's okay because you know what I fuck that bitch I'm in club I know
I'll just be the piece of shit man that is like you know at the end of the day
even if they they argue they'll always they will be naked in a circle in the
woods and stuff like not not sacrificing anything just just like
Like I have an ancestor. She was a witch and and she would they were just drinking a bottle of sack
That's called like a beer or something like that. Mm-hmm singing to the devil and stuff and she she um, she got I think she was hung
It's not so it's not I mean, I'm not kidding. Her name was I'm Mary Sanford. Yeah, Connecticut witch trials
Yeah, but
Nothing. Nothing weird. I'm on sweepy. She's here. I can't even see sweepy because I have her personally blocked because she says
Was terrible shit about man. They're always back and forth psyche. Oh
Bro, this oh, she's like honestly. Oh, look at this dirty motherfucker. You know disgusting
It's like you you just need to learn to learn to save
Fuck all the haters, bro. And it's do you bro. You feel more happier
I am happy. You know who I know you are
You know
But listen, listen, listen, bro, you know who has you at the end day
Like he's eating jalapeno poppers in front of me
Thank you. Come on. I don't do it
You make you look like I want you no more. I want you no more. Yeah, I'll just start myself
I mean just like a copy and just one copy and one
McGriddle
That would be so happy
Because Alex you put you put me through shit tonight. I see them for just for you and stuff
You tell Alex if he does that I'll get real close to the fucking
He sends me McDonald's
She will get a mod but she owes me she owes me McDonald's breakfast
Or else I
Won't even see her comment and you better not tell and if anybody that keeps telling me her comments unless it's your McDonald's is on the way
Get blocked
What do you like for me Donald psyche I like a McRiddle and copies and
Whatever I mean, whatever else they I mean in the morning. Yeah, it sounds so good right now
The Sun's not like uh, I got the luck breakfast. Oh my god. Well, that's pretty good
Like I mean, it's like, you know, it's like, you know, there's
The pancakes and the hash browns
You get everything
Come on all the all the all the content you got out of me. Plus you got oh my god
$200 from clapping me right why does he always come around when I'm around somewhere? Why why?
Me breakfast or I'm never letting me again. You love me. Come on. You love me
I'm gonna fight you over that psyche. He loves me more nigga
Nah, he doesn't mean more
Mexicans
Yeah, nah, he loves me more than you maybe mm-hmm. I just agree with you
No, he loves me. Yeah more than you loves Mexicans cuz he's Puerto Rican that you're closer into race
He's a mutt, bro. He don't know what type of race he is. Yeah, come up here same annual fit right in. Yeah, come up
Yeah
Come up and I'm a grown man fucking conversation
You can be the lucky pier. You know what that means a man. That means
You'll be behind clumsy. I'll be behind you
Whoa, whoa, hell nah, no
Reverse it just reverse it. You'll nah
No, no, no, who knows like, you know
You can have you can have you can have and all your self
Who's modding with their feelings guys
It can one time can a mod mod for me once I mean
It's like no one my mods my mods say I'm just the biggest piece of garbage in the world
But then oh someone says it's one so Canada dry go to hell or you or get a life Canada drive
He blocked them
I mean, how what kind of pussy shit is that like people tell me to die I mean, it's like often I mean, you know
You know how easy it is for someone just to block one person not see their comments again
But it's like you gave me to die. That's fine. But you shouldn't be you didn't have a wrench in my chat telling you that
And that's kind of too much
You're bae. Oh her feelings is bae. They blocked me because you defend me. You never defend me bae
Come on bae. I was born bae love
But I wasn't born last night. Nah, bae loves you
About some other chats about you bro. Bae's always saying oh
Look at this messed up freak
And then I keep kicking him out of the chat and I keep bringing him back
I think they might be a little bipolar
But from what I've seen from a little bit of like the little things that he said about you
He likes me. Yeah
Maybe it's like, you know, he's pulling my hair get my attention. But they are my yeah, he's playing hard to get
Well, I bet I heard he's like a heavy set Mexican guy. I mean, it's like I like Mexican guys
I mean, I really want the more. Oh my god. Why is it gonna be a heavy set masking guy?
How come it can't be a
I don't mind if they have like tattoos and a hairy old white man
I don't want I need to have a gang affiliated person because I have this kitty gang after me and it's like
Well, fuck kitty gang shout out to the real fucking kitty mafia. How about that if you know, you know
Can be in that I can just change my um G to the M. Okay
You should look into that psyche
Yes, yes
Whoa
Yeah
Oh my god, I get a fucking tattoo and pledge my life to them
Bita throws me out this crazy bitch. I mean, let me let me ask you a question about that. Okay
What made you really want to get that fucking?
BKG tattoo on I wanted a little nor tattoo, but I couldn't afford like L a n or e
So I was like, I'll just get the three letters and then I'll get a fix later
Why didn't you fucking wait psyche? Oh gosh, so so so that
2020 I mean, I wish I wish I would have thought of that before I don't know that so the tattoo really don't mean shit to you
It's like some of you regret pretty much
Very I don't have really regrets. I mean it's like tattoos can be covered up, right?
I mean that that part is Lenore, right and I can change it to the door in two seconds
Um, what's the tattoo look like? I never seen it. Okay. Can I see it? It's Lenore. No another BKG. Oh
Shit, I know you had it right there every dog. What the fuck?
Man and be the cheat you like that, bro, that's fuck yeah, I oh
Yeah, and I just mocked me for it like just every was just a total mocking
I was like I just got it cuz I thought I was a cute like I just thought it was her like her show
You and Herbert's great. Where the fuck did this should go left because Arthur said to her
The uncle fuckers shit. Oh my god
I went downhill from there
Or if you don't fucking want to talk about your fucking shit
Don't you shouldn't shit there and bring up your fucking family and talk about this and that on fucking livestream
I don't know. I mean, I kicked him off the show when he said it and well, as you know,
like me and Bita used to be at one point. He was ever mad at him. He's like, no one's
ever mad at the person that says it. He always get mad at me. Oh, I mean, look at this. I
always like the little care in the stick. And I'm like, like, I used to sit there and
It is what it is with her, but look how that shit turned out
Well, we played a clip earlier tonight where she's like
Fuck you and she was like saying I mean she was like hitting on me and stuff
I was like I hardly remember that because she's just been awful to be ever since but yeah
She was time to get on the RV. Hey IP to put me on IP to you. I'll get on the RV. I'll figure out a way, you know
You know
I don't know that shit, Christine, like, at all, at all, at all.
Christine, let's not bring her up with Christine.
No, no, no, no.
I'm not going to say nothing bad, but I just don't understand, like, how...
She's on beta side when she knew it's because
Woman code it's like it's like you know, it's like you know, there's a bro code even though
Ain't you part of that women? Oh, you're gay, right? You're gay, right?
I know I nobody's on my side men aren't women are I don't know. That's why I don't know what the fuck
Yeah, but you know my people on my side are my cats
No, you'll you'll figure it out one day, so I don't think I will
think you kind of know what I think you kind of already know but yeah I know it
there it's everyone's everyone's fucking psychotic and they've turned me crazy
too yeah we all get like that bro including myself well to do myself yeah
Well, you're fine. I mean, it's like, you know, yeah, you have a little bit of a like a lisp and like, you know
Little bit of
I got a gap now not a list motherfuckers. Oh, yeah, you be careful. You don't have a list. You don't
And I guess Alexander has said fuck off to me about the break. Okay. It's okay. It's okay. I don't
I'm funny or probably when I'm starving to death, right? Yeah, he'll say you did
Yeah, booboo kitty doesn't want to know just forget it. I mean, it's not like I
Anybody's donated or it you know for months and months and months. It's fine
Oh, it's okay, ignore Streamlabs classy, he's a dick.
It's not a real person anyway, it's just a robot.
Give me a quick sex site, he's a racial.
You got it, you got it, dude.
Why are there, why are these people here?
Just to laugh at me and like, you know,
I think they would just want to see the final moment,
my final moments in my life.
Oh my God, Streamlabs, don't say my first name.
Don't dox me.
You're my robots.
Stop doxing me.
My own robots doxing me.
Yeah.
I mean, it's like 65 people.
You think someone, I mean, the membership's like $5.
It's not like, you know, is everybody here just like,
like even KZ has sent me five bucks, but it's okay.
It's okay.
It's fine.
RG, come on.
Let me control my robot. Okay, I'll talk to him
RG RG you're lecturing about my own robots. I know how to run a chat RG
Thousands and thousands of hours of streaming. Yeah, so I'll we'll see my website though that I've spent
Thousand yeah bots are bad. Well, you never had a sex robot
Make content. How about, I mean, how about I kick out Tommy fucking
Ginger out of my chat about that band
die
How about that Tommy James how about you to do something besides going to a supermarket and say the fish smells like poo
I mean is I mean is that oh that's content
I mean, I went down to the pier and was more interesting than that you suck
I you had a chance to date Alexandra and you just insult her
I
beg for forgiveness from her and she says I'm you know the spiritual trafficker die Tommy James. Okay, really
Band
I don't care. I don't, I don't think you're very funny or anything. You're fat ginger. You're in my, um, Alexander Mayer's video, too.
I bet the cartoon I made.
It's some content.
I mean, you make some content besides laying on a bed and, you know, his furniture store getting kicked out because you offended the lady.
Did you see? You missed him, RG, when he goes to the supermarket? He's like, oh, have you seen my brother, Sigmund? He's autistic.
The guy's like, no, I haven't seen him.
That was, that was content.
BOOM!
In RG, why don't you make some content too?
Why don't you send me, I mean, but, but...
What have you done for me?
Are you like Tommy?
Well, you know what he just said to me?
It should make some content.
This isn't content!
Are you fucking, are you really, are you really?
This isn't better than that video.
Okay, I quit, I'll quit then.
Oh, hey, Pappas, I'm in the supermarket.
Okay, I tuck your nipple.
The guy's like, oh, please get away from me.
You know, it's like, oh, okay.
Oh, I'm gonna let Alex and their mayors
make me a jam company,
and then I'm gonna call her a dumb whore,
but she'll still hate Psyche more than me.
What, RG?
No, no.
I'm gonna make bacon jam.
It's gonna have THC in it.
And then I have a video I made his great video with Tommy James. He's in a he's he's 300 pounds in a suit of armor-smoking crack
He said he was dumb
And as dumb as he looks
Yeah fat fucker
I mean, geez, I mean, Alexander literally had like a three hour special about how he's like some kind of, you know, alien special alien because he has red hair.
All that means is that he's a devil. I mean, I mean, it's our or like, you know, he has no soul.
It wasn't for Alex, bro. He wouldn't been able to fucking do the things he was able to do on stream for his mom.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah, Alex bought his mom gifts and shit like that.
I mean, it's like, geez.
Yeah, set up for doing that shit.
Like rain, but she's playing.
She bought me.
She she smoked a joint with me and I'm I'm fucking she's like, oh, she's like,
oh, I only donated like 50 bucks to them.
They're like, oh, can you show your cash up?
She's like, sure.
And she just showed like the one transaction, right?
OK, OK, Alex.
Yeah, we know, you know, about the thousands of dollars
and he moved in with you and stuff like that.
We know about it.
Sorry
Geez and show my hold she's show all my all the ones you sent for me, right?
You said you show my you show the whole thing for me, but oh she'll get a show for two
Sam ends like show the whole Tommy gave oh, here's my there's one transaction
Right
I'm the I'm the asshole though. He calls her
I mean, she definitely she called him. I mean, did you see the clip where she says, you know, if this were the plantation days I
Would call Tommy James a and I GG ER
Did anybody hear that joining to play it. Oh
My god, Tommy James is here
What you talk to him for a second I need to like catch my breath
I want to touch his downline and say to his mom fucker.
But.
OK, I don't want to.
I don't feel like looking at your retarded face.
OK, go away.
OK.
Give me another guess.
I mean, who's this?
I don't know about to end the stream.
Hold on.
What?
Hey, what's happened?
Oh, shit.
Let me change that.
Hold on.
I'm gonna get in trouble for
doxie is that is that you're
no no it's okay. That is
picture. Thank god we got the
sun there we go all right psych
he seems like you're having a
little bit of a bad morning
that's true. That morning I
That's that sounds a little drastic. Is that is that actually?
I'll see you in court because
She's fucking nuts
Yeah, what does it what does it mean did you receive paperwork yet? No
No, there you go. She talks and talks and talks and talks listen when she first came around would it everyone tell you
She's going to love bomb you right and then fucking thank you
Everyone told you that and you were surprised when it happened
You're not serious
Oh, he's quiet so far
Well, and then I see you the other day like go Alex hip hip hurry. I was like, what is this guy doing? She's just gonna shit
No, my mind was blown because all the horrible shit she said about you said
That's we peachy
This one's nuts, too, you know that right
You have a thing for females who are out of their fucking mind, apparently
I saw her news leaps
Looks like shut out of Auschwitz. It's getting nice to it. So
Well, I mean she can be the concentration camp guard. I'll be the prisoner. Have you seen like her personality?
Have you watched any olive oils?
She's scary. She was like she's awful. She's a horrible person and you have a thing for horrible women, I think
Alisa fucking
My life because I have so much energy. I have so much good energy
I need to like have something to say to fact you're like fucking ten minutes. Stop being a fag. Well, yeah, you don't need Alex
Yeah, you get out of here
Yeah, you get mad out
How dare he he's literally oh
I'm oh, they're women. How am I I'm a fact Alexander said I'm straight. You don't get it
She said you're gay. What did she say about you today, RG?
Oh, I don't care as you were this other person
psyche I am see
Pokemon that is me
No, she dox me. I'm not happy. What did she say you were?
See Pokemon your see Pokemon. What is who is that Pokemon? I do a political commentary show in the morning
Yeah
Yeah, and she said that she met me. She said she's like I did use psyche because I wanted to learn what a gay person was like and stuff
Because of my you know, and she was in the adult industry
You trying to tell me there's no gay people in the adult industry. Yeah, we've been basically every every guy you fell for hook line
It's sinker as well. Get up get out of here. I didn't fall for shit. I'm smarter than you think
Dork
Go go be pickles
I know Jen, I know, I know.
That's what she said.
She said she was trying to figure out about gay people.
But you know what she said?
She said she was a gay guy and a woman's body
as well as a vampire that was 9,000 years old
and an alien and all kinds of other shit.
Wait, and RG wants to call me names.
RG, really?
Really RG?
Haven't I tried to be on your side RG
and you're insulting me?
Norman Bates. Hey, you're my brother
Yeah alien gay man and vampire. I mean, yes, it's a busy life. She's a lot of people in that head. I
That's how you talk with
Watch how you talk to an actual gay person. Okay. Okay. I'll let you back on watch that. You don't call gay a gay guy faggot
That's a little bit
Metta right you call
KZ a faggot. You don't call me a faggot. Okay. Don't do it again
This Romulus guy fucking cracks me up dude. He comes in in these chats and he bitches emote
To comments that he blocks me I love it. Yes. Anyway psyche in a mod
Why invite Alex into your life if you know, she's crazy and she's just gonna do the same
Do you understand why this had nothing to do with content? Okay out doesn't get it
Doesn't do the contents it wasn't great. We're not is this great content. I don't know he doesn't get it
That's why you're on rumble, and I'm a huge YouTube star that is starving to death, right?
Let me check my phone make sure I only did like about 10 readings, and I'm sure
Okay, and I'm gonna start up to death.
Anyway, RG.
You're eating an amazing breakfast burrito.
We'll come over here, Norman.
We're brothers, right?
I'm more like the, I don't need to eat guys.
I'm on drugs. I don't need to eat.
I'm not letting Tommy James up here.
Oh, what are you doing?
I don't trust gingers, okay?
I saw the South Park episode, what would they do?
They have no soul.
You have mommy issues at the moment? Well...
Happens to the best of us
Yeah, RG RG's here to lap is his own jokes
Call people fag you know fags like a gay person. You know how gay like it didn't get the memo
That's offensive to gay people
It's not wrong. Yeah, okay. Yeah, I know it's I know it's true RG and I respect that you admit that and stuff like that. I
Don't know. What do I do? I wish I play an old old episode of let me see. I want to play that beat as bush episode again
Let me see
I'm gonna play the beat as bush where it says another streamer
Who has on beat us?
Someone who crystal has been reportedly been speaking negatively about in recent days
Regularly guest and fellow streamer who becomes involved in a heated drama
Defending herself against blocking accusations. Let's see what else. I mean, okay
It's bill her name better be be be be
Regular panel member who discusses personal drama in relation. Oh, here it is in Pierce intoxicated an accidental camera incident
Let's see if I can find this one
Hold on
oh i don't see it i don't see her in this episode oh yeah here she is
just watch this for a while i'm just gonna i'm just gonna it's gonna lay down here
you can watch michael and be to talk
yeah yeah my show is a little bit too exclusive for the likes of tommy james and rg right now okay
Especially oh, you're in sold me. Oh, oh come right up. Come right up. Let me put out the red carpet
People that call me terrible names. Okay
No, we're watching a video
No, no in the droop droop I put it in droops channel
Okay, and so there was a fool and there's a you get identified by the face and everything right and it's a hundred percent
You can just take some of their random
Right, no, no, no, yeah
Well, I'm wearing like a gray shirt, so it would be known if it was me. Yes, that was great
She was wearing a very long t-shirt and then there's a big black bush underneath her cooch
while she was changing her underwear.
What's that?
Oh, it's like a gray, it's like a gray underwear.
It was like, it was like the shadow of the tent.
You're all fan, this is all your fantasy, guys.
It's a gray underwear.
It's a gray and your hair is to the right.
You're right.
I'm living in the Matrix.
Your hair is to the right side.
I just saw the video.
It's a gray underwear.
Everyone, have Arthur put on his Discord?
That is like, that is pornography.
It's not allowed on Discord.
I
Punked you all that was me in a wig you just saw my butthole guys
You also my butthole, okay?
All you saw was my butthole
Me and me should do my underwear. I I was actually on the bitty beat his kitty gang count, okay?
All you guys saw my but guys that's my butthole that is that was me
See, I'm a bit of a friend by the way.
Look at it.
As beta sometimes, because I fantasize
that I'm beta sometimes, okay?
You can see shit.
I'm telling you.
I know, I know.
You're wrong about everything so far.
My butthole does have a clip
My butthole is like very long and like has a nice little
I have guys on every Halloween I dress like Cher, okay, and I do
What's the share song? Let's just share a song hold on
I got you know this other it's like I got you babe. I got you babe
That's and I think Sonny and Cher and I dress like Cher every Halloween
That was me guys. Yeah, yeah, you guys all got fucking punked. That was me
Sorry be the okay, the jig is up it was
I believe my Michael Michael Michael nice and me now Michael you didn't make sure your balls
No
Yes, yes, I need to see your balls and your butthole to be even
Do you saw you saw everything's on mine? You saw mine, so I need to see yours now Michael
Don't tell Michael you're telling my secrets now you guys know I'm a female to male transsexual
No, yeah
I'm on male hormones guys. Look all this beard is to see how it doesn't grow in right
I'm a female to male. That was me. I
Worse I wear a wig like a chair. That was me Michael
Oh beat beat is just trying to protect me. She's trying to protect me
and then this guy who called
because I lasered my whole
fucking body. I don't have
anything like that, but I did
have like I did. I did. I
fucking want a little rock.
You showed your fucking
and then I'm wearing a long
shirt and I fell down. Oh, you
fell down. Are you okay? That
was me. That was me. Yeah, I
karaoke show
What happened guys? I go. What's the share song? Oh, I don't know. It's not it's not frozen
It's what's the share song?
Thanks, you're they share Michael you like share
Okay, Michael's gay. I'm so I was saying Michael's gay. Okay. He likes shit only only gay only gay people like here
Michael Michael, it's okay. Michael. It's okay if you're gay Michael's my sonnie to my share. I got you, babe
Say babe, I got you babe. Say it Michael man. Say it one time
What? What do you want to say? Babe, I got you, babe.
Babe, I got you, babe.
Preston, peace, man.
So, yeah.
So, Michael, let me do a setting and a share.
We do a drag show where I dress as Cher.
This is like Sonny Michael is actually a female to male transsexual. I'm a male to female
We are I'm not Michael actually a vagina. I have a he's a vagina. I have a dick
But what what do you want? Oh, that was a replay. Yeah
What do you think Michael came back to life? No, I was just listening to you
Hold on that
Yeah, dude Michael passed away, bro
Yeah, he passed away
What though? I know
Yeah, bro. He passed away a couple months ago man. I thought I was a
Month ago he passed away almost a year ago. Do you think it's almost a year now? Yeah
What month did he pass away? I don't July. I think it was July
Wow
Yeah, clumsy I
The whole what is it the obituary came out?
His wife or
She came out and then she was like if we could please just stop talking about him
He was a good guy, and he really loves
Before anybody else and they keep like he keeps saying oh, I'm not allowed to talk about him
We're trying to summon his spirit and stuff
Go fuck yourselves, he loved me.
He couldn't stand them bitches, but he liked me.
Jeez, tell me who to talk about.
You should hear how they talked about him on the show.
Oh my goodness, when he passed away,
clumsy beetle was like, yeah, okay, all right,
you know, he's gone, okay, okay, so what?
He was a piece of shit to my friend.
Hold on hold on. So that's who she was talking about the whole time see cuz that I yeah, I was like that's pro bro
Wow all because like whatever he had a situation with another woman
Beedah's like, oh, he's a piece of shit. Fuck him.
Oh, I remember. I remember.
Yeah, everyone called me that.
Yeah, pretty much Murna.
Like, even after he passed away, people were like,
Beedah was still shitting on him.
Like, what the fuck?
Well, yeah, because that's when I was so cool with Beedah
and he would even join the panel, bro,
and he would chill over there,
and Beedah would fucking shit on him some time.
Yeah?
I don't know.
He's like, what a bitch.
Fuck him.
He's like, oh, such a scumbag.
Betch be the wouldn't be that bad bro is she would just fucking
Girl lovely that too, but like girl up to her
Well the grow up to but girl up, you know how I tell like one fuckers like man up to your shit like girl up like
You know when you fuck up, you know when you fuck up though
She never admits it. No, you know what her excuse is. Oh, but that's all other people that are worse than me
My show about how she's being bullet. I mean, it's like it sounds like me. I mean, it's like
Do I have a troll army defending me? No
Mm-hmm. Yeah, she makes that little like trill a trill sound
It's nice to have that fucking type of energy though until salmon start fucking
But yeah
Are you a bitch?
A bitch, you're a fucking bitch.
Bro, you know what's funny is that
B does fucking disrespect get the fuck out of fucking Samman
and he's also do the same thing back, bro.
And they're like.
Oh yeah, and they're cool.
Oh, but me, I'm like, I'm fucking a garbage.
I'm just garbage, right?
Yeah, if if I'm not wrong, I swear, bro
I think I think Sam and was jealous of the fact that I was cool with Vita and the way like
Oh, but the thing about people the thing about Arthur is that I'm married, bro
Like I don't come at these females like nasty or any pictures or whatever, you know, I'm staying like
Yeah, I'll talk to you like a friend though, you know I'm saying like
I
Does he does bro like honestly like he doesn't even lay off
She needs to lay off the liquor to lay off the internet
needs to fucking eat a bowl
cereal
Mr.. Eat a bowl of cereal about to say something my fault
With rap poison
Oh my god, you should have seen last night these three people they were talking about us me
Psyche just let Arthur and clumsy just talk shit about me. I told you, this is why I hate Psyche.
Because he don't want to tell people to shut up about me. I thought Psyche cared about us.
Psyche said yes. Psyche asked me.
Oh, I'm such a fucking Arab bitch.
And someone's in that bitch a fucking rug homie such a flyer
Yo Marco Rubio if you're listening yo send the drone a Cali right look for this fucking bitch called be the and get rich
Imagine fucking with her with a drone
Oh, no, let me get some real quick and get set.
Yeah, we have an Arthur
You lead
It's a icky yeah, okay, I'm sure
Now you good you good you good you like no one
What's wrong doc none talk about that shit, what's up, okay?
Now what's wrong psyche on some real shit. What's up, man?
You you want a motherfucker to tell you how it is
What's up? What's on your mind?
It's just like it's like
Like everyone likes each other and it's like no one likes me. It's like
There's a lot of you that fuck with you psyche, but right now you're this in the midst of fucking
Warfare and people are trying to have everyone turn again
But it's fine. It's like I can't even like express any feelings and then it's like, oh
He's he's uh, he's coercing and he's manipulating and stuff like that. I'm just
You're suffering. I don't know. I was like, I just think that I stay on my mouth has nothing to do with you
But I put everything into this I put everything I put everything into it and it's like
It's like people just want to see me like die like I really they do
That's what I feel like
I wouldn't say exactly they want you to, you know, fucking perish and, you know what I mean?
I can't express that because then it's like, oh, he's
But they really would I mean they really would like it's like I just can't even like express it in another way. They'd be
Happy, I mean they're striking my champ. I suppose if friends are striking my champ like
Friends like that who needs enemies, right?
But see psyche you let people see this side of you. They're gonna keep on doing that shit
Yeah, I guess what we die then fucking pull a trigger and done
It's not that serious though psyche is a fucking internet
Everybody it's like it's like all this like mine
Everybody like just wait. Did I know I know on it, right? It's like you mean
Some people will have like some people that like them and stuff like that. It's like who do I have? I've said I
Mean what that's my friend. No you you you have a lot more people behind you and like I told you before bro even the
People I talked about it. There's people that care about you bro. There. No, there is
There is you might have a like a lot more haters
See like the ratio of like likes to dislikes them if you've ever seen somebody like
With like 700 views with like five or six likes. I
Mean, it's like I like it really it's like
You know they do that for
That's not even a thing cost anything just a light is that it was like make it say because they don't but it's like
They're they're watching it like I had literally
On one video like over a thousand views and like under 10 likes
Yeah, what else am I supposed to say? It's like
Like it's like, that's like such a astronomical ratio of like people that are just like, don't
even care.
It's like, you know what, and I can respect that if you're like, you know, I understand
that they're kind of using your fucking emotions on me, it's like, it's like, what Sam, Sam
man makes more money off my content than I do, sweeping is more likes on my content
than I get on my content.
They, it's like, they're jealous of you bro. They're jealous of you though.
Listen though, listen. They're jealous of you. They're jealous of you, foe. They're jealous.
Not really that because apparently I'm just like what else would you call it?
What would you call it someone that clips you someone that says oh this and that and this
Just like a locale kind of thing. It's like okay, but it's coming from someone that can't even show their fucking face, right?
But it's like what?
It's coming
face and they're like
Way more popular than me. It's like it's like I like put everything out there. I do everything. I show everything and it's like
That's you think everyone that watches certain people likes them just like you you know
It's like not like at least like somebody like me and it's like go to hell Tommy James. Like I don't want to talk to you. I
Mean really
I don't want to talk to Sam and Tommy James.
Sam, just clip my content.
Just say, oh, look how disgusting he looks after a year.
Like, oh, and that's because of like what?
Meth instead of like, you know, Bita and Alexandra
and just the thousands of trolls constantly like,
you know, like putting me down and like.
It's going to come with this IP.
It's going to come with the, you know why?
Because you put in introduce yourself to IP too.
That's why.
Well, yeah, and then that is like basically the what a suicide network, but so is Alejandro and Vita
But but now I'm in trouble for saying that you know, whatever
IP to
do bro
How long you been streaming psyche before you came around over here I
Started here because I could know cuz I cuz even her name
girl that she's like real pretty she has tattoos. No, no, no.
Alisa?
She always comes on a summer summer. Oh summer. Yeah, she's talked about she's talked about how long she's known you and she didn't you she said before
They said knew me longer than they do because people always say like I like for example Alexander says
Oh, well beat has been putting us together against each other for a year. No, it wasn't a year
We met and we met in like a fucking October. So let me see
What what you're just gonna make fun of me all night on the on your show. Yeah, he did he want. Yeah, he wants something for his fucking
Yeah, he don't got nothing to talk about that's why I don't feel like talking to you right now
Okay, you're just gonna be sound like a recharge. He's a big ass
And fucking have KZ making fun of me at this point. Yeah, man
What I tell you bro everywhere I go, bro, you fucking try to come up and try to top bro like
grow the fuck up already nigga it's early in the fucking morning you're a two-face because
you're like you're nice to me like when you talk to me because i'm like really susceptible to
people being nice to me when they talk to me and stand my no fuck with you stand my no fuck with
you psyche i'm sorry i know i know i know it's just like everyone just
Me I don't give a fuck month. What is my clown me cuz
Xen guys are likable, I mean it's like some people make like you never did nothing wrong to me, bro
Just because someone hates you and I'm cool with them like told him that's not that's nothing against me
You know, I understand what people are coming from how they feel, but you know what you ain't did nothing wrong to me
I'm sorry that you
I mean, I think I must have like what I did I I've done something I must have done something very wrong
I mean to be treated like this. I mean, it's like
nah
I guess
What's wrong? It's okay. I'm just some some people are just full of jealousy and envy bro
Well, it's like what is there anything else about I'm nothing. I mean, it's like what just because I'm basically just getting kicked in the
I mean, it's a what to be jealous of I don't understand. It's like
Look at your past videos on how fun you used to have look look how much fun used to have back in the day
I did but that was that I was delusional because I was like I ignored all the shit that was being said and like
You know, that's why maybe that's who should go back to you is ignoring
I mean, it's like basically really it's like like I said, I don't have much like this is like my like life
And then it's like I don't know what I'm like, what am I gonna do anymore?
No, I I understand and only you know what you want big dog. You know I'm saying only only you know what you want
I can't I don't know what I want anymore because it's like
Well, you're gonna have to figure that out yourself. You know, I'm saying
Okay, what I do
This no
But nothing no, it's like what is it? You know, like sometimes pain is preferable to nothing
Yeah
some people
If you like if someone like feels nothing
Right just to feel pain is like yeah, it's like the people turn to pain for happiness. I I fully understand
fully understand
But you're an issue. Well, I just feel like I'm like, you know, no one care. Um, I feel like I'm gonna
Don't don't let this there and it should get too much. Thank you so much